Guide to the Witchcraft and possession-related movie posters, lobby cards, and other cinema memorabilia, 1916-2015.
Witchcraft and possession-related movie posters, lobby cards, and other cinema memorabilia,
- 1980-1989
  - The Devil in Miss Jones II, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 38)
  - Descenso a los infiernos, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 38)
    Original U.S. title: Dream Demon
    Uruguay
  - Elvira: Mistress of the Dark, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 38)
  - L'esorcista III, 1989; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 44)
    Original U.S. title: The Exorcist III
  - Tanz der Teufel, 1981 (Mapcase-folder 38)
    Original U.S. title: The Evil Dead
  - Fear No Evil, 1981; 8 items (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Fear No Evil, 1981 (Mapcase-folder 39)
  - Lucifer, 1981 (Mapcase-folder 39)
    Original U.S. title: Fear No Evil
  - Witch Hunt, 1981 (Box exhibit?)
    From Cannes Festival
    Original Norwegian title: Forflgelsen
  - Caccia Alla Strega, 1981 (Mapcase-folder 36)
    Witch Hunt
  - Caccia Alla Strega, 1981; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 44)
  - Il Villaggio Delle Streghe, 1987 (Mapcase-folder 36)
    Original U.S. title: From a Whisper to a Scream
  - The Offspring, 1987 (Mapcase-folder 39)
  - Non aprite quel cancello, 1987; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 44)
    Original U.S. title: The Gate
  - Un diavolo di ragazza, 1989; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 44)
    Original U.S. title: Girlfriend From Hell
  - The Hearse, 1980 (Mapcase-folder 39)
    Bowers, George
  - Hell Night, 1981 (Mapcase-folder 39)
  - Incubus, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 36)
    Cassavettes, John
  - Incubus, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 36)
  - Incubus, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 36)
  - The Incubus, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 39)
  - Inferno, 1980 (Mapcase-folder 39)
  - Invitation to Hell, 1984 (Mapcase-folder 36)
  - Kiki La Petite Sorcire, 1989 (Mapcase-folder 36)
    Japanese animated feature
    Kiki's Delivery Service
    Original Japanese title: Majo no takkybin
  - Kiki's Delivery Service, 1989 (Mapcase-folder 36)
    Title on posters appears in Japanese characters. Japanese animated feature.
  - Wie die Kleine Hexe das Zaubern Lernter, 1986 (Mapcase-folder 37)
    Original Czechoslovakian title: Mala Carodejnice
  - La Piccola Strega, 1986 (Mapcase-folder 39)
  - Manhattan Baby, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 39)
    Original Italian title: Il malocchio
  - La mansin de los muertos vivientes, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 40)
  - Mia Moglie una Strega, 1981; 9 items (Mapcase-folder 37)
  - Mia Moglie una Strega, 1981; 1 items (Mapcase-folder 37)
  - Mia Moglie una Strega, 1981; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 44)
  - Mia Moglie una Strega, 1981; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 44)
  - Le Moine et la Sorcire, 1987; 10 items (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Sorceress
    Photographs
  - Sorceress, 1987 (Mapcase-folder 40)
    Original French title: Le moine et la sorcire
  - La Monaca del Peccato, 1986; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 44)
    Convent of Sinners
  - Necropolis, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 40)
  - Night Vision, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Night Visitor, 1989 (Mapcase-folder 40)
  - Omen III: The Final Conflict, 1981 (Mapcase-folder 39)
  - The Gates of Hell, 1980 (Mapcase-folder 40)
    Original Italian title: Paura nella citt dei morti viventi
  - Miedo en la ciudad de los muertos vivientes, 1980 (Mapcase-folder 40)
  - Il piccolo diavolo, 1988; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 45)
  - Possession, 1981 (Mapcase-folder 37)
  - Possession, 1983 (Mapcase-folder 40)
  - Prime Evil, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Knez Tame, 1987 (Mapcase-folder 37)
    Original U.S. title: Prince of Darkness
  - Il signore del male, 1987; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 45)
  - Witch from Nepal, 1986 (Mapcase-folder 40)
    Original title: Qi Yuan
  - La Reine de la Magie Noire, 1983 (Mapcase-folder 37)
    Original U.S. title: The Queen of Black Magic
  - El Enigma del Hechicero, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 40)
    Original U.K. title: The Raggedy Rawney
    Gypsies
  - Rendez-moi ma peau..., 1980; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 45)
    Give Me Back My Skin
  - Satanína Oštríca, 1984 (Mapcase-folder 37)
    Original U.S. title: Satan's Blade
  - Scream Greats, 1986 (Mapcase-folder 41)
    Advertisment for video collection.
  - Las sobrinas del diablo, 1983 (Mapcase-folder 41)
  - Carobnice Blizanke is Lemura, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 37)
    Original U.S. title: Sorceress
  - Sorceress, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 41)
  - Under the Sun of Satan, 1987 (Mapcase-folder 41)
    Original French title: Sous le soleil de Satan
  - Spellbinder, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 41)
  - Witch Story, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Superstition 2
    Original Italian title: Streghe
  - Streghe, 1989 (Mapcase-folder 37)
  - Streghe, 1989; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 45)
  - Superstition, 1982; 10 items (Box 2, Folder 10)
    aka The Witch
  - The Witch, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Original Canadian title: Superstition
  - Superstition, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 41)
    Canada
  - Superstition, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 41)
  - The Witch, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 41)
  - La Casa de Mary, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 41)
    Original Canadian title: Superstition, aka The Witch
  - La Spada E La Magia, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 37)
    Original U.S. title: The Sword and the Sorcerer
  - Teen Witch, 1989 (Mapcase-folder 42)
  - Delirium House - La casa del delirio, 1985; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 45)
    Original U.S. title: Terror
  - Delirium House - La casa del delirio, 1985 (Mapcase-folder 37)
  - Delirium House - La casa del delirio, 1985 (Mapcase-folder 37)
  - Three Sovereigns for Sarah, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Troll, 1986 (Mapcase-folder 42)
  - Il Trono di Fuoco, 1983 (Mapcase-folder 41)
    The Throne of Fire
    Prosperi, Franco
  - El Trono del Fuego, 1983 (Mapcase-folder 41)
  - El Trono del Fuego, 1983 (Mapcase-folder 41)
  - The Unholy, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 42)
  - Soprannaturale, 1988; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 45)
    Original U.S. title: The Unholy
  - Veerana, 1988; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 42)
    India
  - La vera storia della monaca di Monza, 1980 (Mapcase-folder 37)
  - Opatica iz Monce, 1980 (Mapcase-folder 37)
    Original Italian title: La vera storia della monaca di Monza
  - La vera storia della monaca di Monza, 1980 (Mapcase-folder 42)
  - La Visione del Sabba, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 37)
    The Witches’ Sabbath
  - Sabba—Die Hexe, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 41)
    Original Italian title: La Visione del Sabba
  - La Sorcire, 1988; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 45)
    Bellocchio, Marco, 1939-
  - The Warrior and the Sorceress, 1984 (Mapcase-folder 42)
  - Wicked Stepmother, 1989 (Mapcase-folder 42)
  - The Witch, 1980 (Mapcase-folder 37)
  - The Witch, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 42)
  - Witchboard, 1986 (Mapcase-folder 42)
  - Spiritika, 1986; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 45)
    Original U.S. title: Witchboard
  - Witchcraft, 1988; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 42)
  - Witches of Eastwick, 1987 (Mapcase-folder 42)
  - La Streghe di Eastwick, 1987; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 45)
    Original U.S title: The Witches of Eastwick
  - Witchtrap, 1989 (Mapcase-folder 42)
    The Presence, The Haunted
- 1990-1999
  - Satan Returns, 1996 (Mapcase-folder 47)
    Original Chinese title: 666: Mo gui fu huo
  - 976 Chiamata per il Diavolo 2, Il Fattore Astrale, 1992; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 50)
    976-EVIL II, aka 976-EVIL 2: The Astral Factor
    Original Italian Title: 976 Chiamata per il Diavolo 2, Il Fattore Astrale
  - Un Amour de Sorcire, 1997 (Mapcase-folder 50)
    Witch Way Love
  - Black Magic Woman, 1991 (Mapcase-folder 47)
  - La Casa 5, 1990 (Mapcase-folder 50)
  - La Casa 7, 1990 (Mapcase-folder 50)
  - Evil Black Magic, 1992 (Mapcase-folder 47)
    Original Chinese title: Chu nu de you huo
  - The Craft, 1996; 8 items (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Giovani Streghe, 1996 (Mapcase-folder 46)
    Original U.S. title: The Craft
  - The Craft, 1996; Double-sided (Mapcase-folder 47)
  - Jovenes y Brujas, 1996 (Mapcase-folder 47)
  - The Crucible, 1996 (Mapcase-folder 47)
    Adaptation of Arthur Miller's The Crucible
    Day-Lewis, Daniel
    Ryder, Winona
  - Las Brujas de Salem, 1996; Double-sided (Mapcase-folder 47)
    Adaptation of Arthur Miller's The Crucible.
    Original U.S. title: The Crucible
  - Witch Hunter, 1996 (Mapcase-folder 47)
  - El Hijo de Satan, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Original U.K. Title: The Devil's Child
  - El Dia de la Bestia, 1995 (Mapcase-folder 47)
    The Day of the Beast
  - Double, Double Toil and Trouble, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    T.V. Guide
    Olsen, Mary Kate
    Olsen, Ashley
  - The First Power, 1990 (Mapcase-folder 47)
  - El Primier Poder, 1990 (Mapcase-folder 47)
    Original U.S. title: The First Power
  - Pentagram, 1990 (Mapcase-folder 50)
  - Four Rooms, 1995 (Mapcase-folder 47)
  - The Haunting of Morella, 1990 (Mapcase-folder 47)
  - Hocus Pocus, 1993 (Mapcase-folder 47)
  - Kirikou et la Sorcire, 1998 (Mapcase-folder 50)
    France/Belgium/Luxembourg co-production
    Kirikou and the Sorceress
    Africa
  - Kirik e la Strega Karab, 1998 (Mapcase-folder 50)
    Original French title: Kirikou et la Sorcire
  - Khoon Ki Pyasi, 1996; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - La Nona Porta, 1999 (Mapcase-folder 46)
    Original U.S. title: The Ninth Gate
  - Omen IV, 1991 (Mapcase-folder 46)
  - Paradise Lost: The Child Murders at Robin Hood Hills, 1996 (Mapcase-folder 48)
    Documentary
    Murder
  - The Possession of Michael D., 1995 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Practical Magic, 1998 (Mapcase-folder 48)
  - Practical Magic, 1998 (Mapcase-folder 48)
  - Repossessed, 1990; 10 items (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Repossessed, 1990 (Mapcase-folder 48)
  - Y Dnde Est el Exorcista?, 1990 (Mapcase-folder 48)
    Original U.S. title: Repossessed
  - Riposseduta, 1990; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 50)
  - La Secta, 1991; 12 items (Box 2, Folder 11)
    The Devil's Daughter, aka The Sect
    Original Italian title: La Setta
  - La Secta, 1991 (Mapcase-folder 48)
  - La Secta, 1991 (Mapcase-folder 50)
  - Sorceress, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Summer of Sam, 1999 (Mapcase-folder 49)
    Lee, Spike
  - Tanz der Dmonen, 1990 (Mapcase-folder 49)
    Demon Wind
  - Teenage Exorcist, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Thinner, 1996 (Mapcase-folder 49)
  - Witchcraft Part 2: The Temptress, 1990 (Mapcase-folder 49)
  - Witchcraft III: The Kiss of Death, 1991 (Mapcase-folder 49)
  - Witchcraft IV: Virgin Heart, 1992 (Mapcase-folder 49)
  - The Witches, 1990 (Mapcase-folder 46)
  - The Witches, 1990 (Mapcase-folder 49)
  - Las Brujas, 1990 (Mapcase-folder 49)
    Original U.S. title: The Witches
  - Witches are Bitches, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Le Streghe del Sesso, 1996 (Mapcase-folder 48)
    Original U.S. title: Witches Are Bitches
  - Witch Hunt, 1994 (Box 5, Mapcase-folder 14)
    Hopper, Dennis, 1936-2010
- 2000-2009
  - Bewitched, 2005 (Mapcase-folder 51)
  - Bless the Child, 2000 (Mapcase-folder 51)
  - El Llamado, 2000 (Mapcase-folder 51)
    Original U.S. title: The Calling
  - The Covenant, 2006 (Mapcase-folder 51)
  - The Chronicles of Narnia: The Lion the Witch and the Wardrobe, 2005 (Mapcase-folder 51)
  - Drag Me To Hell, 2009; Double-sided (Mapcase-folder 51)
  - Eko Eko Azarak, 2005 (Mapcase-folder 51)
    For DVD set of series
  - The Exorcism of Emily Rose, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Exorcism of Emily Rose, 2005; Double-sided (Mapcase-folder 51)
  - Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire, 2005; Double-sided (Mapcase-folder 51)
  - Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, 2009; Double-sided (Mapcase-folder 51)
  - Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban, 2004 (Mapcase-folder 53)
  - Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone, 2001 (Mapcase-folder 51)
  - Hex, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Hex, 2004; Vinyl (Mapcase-folder 57)
    Banners
  - Da Hip Hop Witch, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Jennifer's Body, 2009 (Mapcase-folder 52)
  - Just Visiting, 2001; Double-sided (Mapcase-folder 52)
  - Lady Death, 2003 (Mapcase-folder 52)
  - The Omen, 2006 (Mapcase-folder 52)
  - The Omen, 2006; Double-sided (Mapcase-folder 52)
  - Salem's Daughter, 2009 (Mapcase-folder 52)
    Comic book
  - La Terza Madre, 2007 (Mapcase-folder 52)
    Mother of Tears
  - La Terza Madre, 2007 (Mapcase-folder 52)
  - Twitches Too, 2007 (Mapcase-folder 52)
  - The Unborn, 2008 (Mapcase-folder 52)
  - The Wicker Man, 2006; Double-sided (Mapcase-folder 52)
- 2010-2018
  - The Baby, 2014 (Mapcase-folder 54)
  - Beautiful Creatures, 2013 (Mapcase-folder 54)
  - Delaware Tea Party, 2010; MU-1342 (Box 1)
    T-Shirts
  - Deliver Us From Evil, 2014 (Mapcase-folder 54)
  - Devil, 2010 (Mapcase-folder 54)
  - The Devil Inside, 2012 (Mapcase-folder 54)
  - Con el Diable Adentro, 2012 (Mapcase-folder 54)
    Original U.S. title: The Devil Inside
  - Devil's Due, 2014 (Mapcase-folder 54)
  - El Anticristo, 2010 (Mapcase-folder 54)
    Original Spanish title: Exorcismus
  - Hansel and Gretel: Witch Hunters, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Harry Potter and the Deathly Hollows Part 2, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Lenticular posters
  - Into the Woods, 2014; Vinyl (Mapcase-folder 57)
  - The Last Exorcism, 2010; 2 sheets; Double-sided, style A, style B (Mapcase-folder 55)
  - Last Exorcism Part II, 2013; Vinyl (Mapcase-folder 57)
  - Last Exorcism Part II, 2013; Double-sided (Mapcase-folder 55)
  - The Lords of Salem, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Maleficent, 2013; Double-sided (Mapcase-folder 55)
  - Maleficent, 2013; Vinyl (Mapcase-folder 55)
  - Mirror Mirror, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - O'Donnell, Christine, 2010; MU-1343; Image of a witch. (Box 1)
    T-shirts
  - Oz the Great and Powerful, 2013 (Mapcase-folder 55)
  - ParaNorman, 2012; 2 sheets; Double-sided, style A, style B (Mapcase-folder 55)
  - The Possession, 2012; 2 sheets; Double-sided, style B (Mapcase-folder 55)
  - The Possession of Michael King, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - The Possession of Michael King, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Cup coasters
  - War Witch, 2012 (Mapcase-folder 56)
    Original title: Rebelle
  - The Rite, 2011; Double-sided (Mapcase-folder 56)
  - Salem, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Season of the Witch, 2010; 3 sheets; Double-sided, style A, style B (Mapcase-folder 56)
  - The Secret Circle, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Snow White and the Huntsman, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Witches of East End, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Witches of East End, 2013 (Mapcase-folder 57)
  - Les Sorciers de Waverly Place, 2010 (Mapcase-folder 56)
    Original English title: The Wizards of Waverly Place
  - Witching and Bitching, 2013 (Mapcase-folder 56)
    de la Iglesia, lex